What?
No. no.
No. no. no.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
What's going on?
Does anybody know what happened?
They're saying there's
some kind of exposure.
- Exposure to what?
- Haven't said.
All we know is a few kids have
died and a daycare worker too.
Every second we wait.
it gets worse!
- I'm sorry.
- Please! Come on.
Do you have kids?
- I'm sorry.
You gotta be able
to tell us something.
- Hey!
- No. I gotta go back!
- Can't let you through. ma'am.
It's not safe.
- No! I gotta get...
- It's not safe.
My daughter's inside!
You'll have to wait
with everyone else
till hazmat's cleared the scene.
- Let me go!
No!
Oh. God. no!
It's my baby!
It's my boy!
Walt!
Walt! Walt!
No. no. no. no.
no. no. no. no. no.
Hey. what are you
doing back here?
I already told you.
you can't be here.
- Sorry.
Sorry. I... I just...
I can't find my kid.
Excuse me.
you're the owner. right?
- Yeah.
- Do you know this woman?
She says her kid goes here.
No. I've never seen her
before in my life.
All right. drop the bag
and put your hands
where I can see them.
Nice and slow.
- Ron Nadalini.
Newburgh Police.
Thanks for making the trek.
- Yeah.
What do we know. Ron?
- Nothing good.
Looks like two kids.
four years old.
must have found the drugs
back behind the daycare.
Dug out a brick and opened it.
They didn't know.
Died on site.
What kind of crew drops
their product behind a daycare?
The kind we're
gonna bring in. yeah?
Oh. man.
Fentanyl?
That's right.
After the kids went down.
aide died trying to revive them.
Killed during CPR.
So this is a potent strain.
Street name Pompeii.
ODs all over the northeast
with the same story...
bodies left frozen in position.
That's how quick they die.
We know where it's coming from?
Not local.
None of my guys can pinpoint
what state it's coming from.
Neither can our CIs.
Why we called you all.
But I'd start with
the crew's gopher.
We got her in
a squad car in front.
I already told the cops
I don't know anything.
OK. well. you can
either talk to us
or beg the judge for leniency.
but those ODs
are gonna fall on you
unless you cooperate.
Now. we both know that you are
a low man on the totem pole.
You had a job
to pick up the drugs.
So you can either tell us
who those drugs belong to.
or the prosecution will prove
that they were yours.
and then three felony murders
are gonna land on you.
- No. it... it...
it was not like that.
It's... you see.
what happened was. I. um...
I heard about those kids.
and people were saying
they found a package.
and I...
I shouldn't have done it...
it was stupid...
but I'm... I'm an addict. OK?
That's why I was back there.
- Emily. stop.
Those kids found
the drugs at a dead drop.
The neighbors spotted you
several times.
said you parked over there.
walk along the house.
pick up the package. and go.
Now. this is what
the jury is gonna see.
Kimberly Mitchell.
She's the daycare worker
that died trying
to save the kids
that were killed by the drugs
you were supposed to pick up.
- Stop it.
- Look.
That's Grace.
That's Walt.
just four years old.
They are no longer here
because of what you did.
Who do those drugs belong to?
I don't know.
My boyfriend.
He's... he's like...
he's nobody.
He sells.
He... it... my job is
I pick up the package
and I bring it to him.
OK. we'll deal
with your boyfriend.
but we're not the cops.
We're the FBI.
We need to know the source
of the supply.
So. again.
whose drugs were those?
- I don't know.
I swear. Um...
One time. I...
I got here early.
and I saw the car
that made the drop off.
Can you describe it to me?
Grace Kessler.
she wanted to be a gymnast.
Next week would have
been her birthday.
She would have been
five years old.
Walt Calloway wanted
to be a firefighter.
just like his father.
This morning. their parents
got the worst news
of their lives.
along with two dozen
other families
across the northeast
who have lost family members
to a deadly strain
of fentanyl called Pompeii.
I demand to know where
these drugs are coming from
so that we can
shut this operation down.
OK. so the drug mule
that OA interviewed claims
that she saw the bricks
dropped off
behind the daycare by someone
driving a black Caprice.
The daycare
has security cameras.
We've been combing through
footage from the past few days.
Take a look at this.
All right.
there's the black Caprice.
Switching angles
to behind the daycare.
Here's our guy in the
backyard making the drop.
Can we get an ID?
Not enough for facial rec.
And the plates are stolen.
- Hey.
Hey. hey. hey.
We may have gotten a break.
NYPD just pulled that car over
in Briarwood.
Good.
Have them hold the driver
until we can get a team there.
Thanks.
FBI.
We need to inspect your vehicle.
You need a warrant for that.
Not when there's
an active AMBER Alert
and your car matches the
description of the vehicle.
Pop the trunk.
- Come on.
You see a kid in my car?
That's why I'm asking you
to pop the trunk.
Or we can stay here
until we get the warrant
you're so concerned about.
OK.
Nope.
All clear.
OK. you're good to go.
Camera's in place and recording.
Well. let's see who this guy
kicks up to. yeah?
I got eyes on
a second individual
walking out of the residence.
He must have realized we found
their drop spot at the daycare.
Looks like they're pulling back
all their runners.
Oy. Diego. chill. chill. chill.
There's no need
for that. a'ight?
You're two hours late.
I swear to you.
it was an AMBER Alert.
Cops pulled me over
looking for some kid.
- What alert?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
OK. that is Diego Torres.
25. long sheet.
Drugs and weapons charges.
Well. there's our bigger fish.
Everybody hang back till
we got eyes on the drugs.
Then we move in.
- And they pulled you over?
- Yeah.
But. yo.
they didn't find the trap.
We're clean. baby.
See?
- Whatever. man.
You always
got some kind of story.
Get this in the bag
and get it inside.
And there's
the rest of our product.
Same stamp as the drugs
at the crime scene.
This has got to be one
of the stash houses.
All units. move in.
- FBI!
Nobody move!
Hands where we can see them.
We've got exposed powder.
I would not do that
if I were you.
- Or what?
- You know exactly what.
You start shooting.
everybody in here dies
from exposure.
Put your weapons down.
Now!
- Man's right.
Hands up.
Hey!
- I'm on it.
Diego Torres.
you're under arrest.
Possession. distribution.
assault and battery.
extortion. larceny.
quite a diversified
portfolio. Diego.
Two innocent four-year-olds
lost their lives this morning.
along with their teacher.
We will prove that their deaths
were caused by your product.
dropped off by a vehicle tracked
back to your stash house.
This will all come down
on your head.
You don't scare me.
Your wife. Lillian.
she's on parole. right?
Don't talk about my wife.
We charge you today.
we violate her parole for
associating with criminals.
She will be held without bail.
Lily's got nothing
to do with this.
I'm not done.
Once we pick up
your wife and your kids.
Marisol and Rafael.
suddenly they have
no parental guardian.
They will be placed
in foster care.
and you will not see them again.
You bitch.
"You bitch?"
I'm trying to help you.
You're at a crossroads. Diego.
You can either
watch your whole family
be torn apart from behind bars
or give me a name.
Who do you kick up to?
You do that.
and you walk out of here.
You can have dinner tonight
with Lily and the kids.
All you got to do
is give me his name.
Hector Vega.
OK. what do we know
about Hector Vega?
Uh. DEA sent over a list
of probable stash houses.
allegedly all run by Vega.
And we think Vega is
responsible for the deaths
in Newburgh this morning?
- Looking like it.
So Vega started dealing
in Jersey. street level.
Tried but acquitted.
Appears he's built
himself up since then.
He's made a name for himself
moving fent from New York City
to upstate dealers and beyond.
Yeah. he slipped
their hook a few times.
but the DEA says that Vega
runs a pretty tight op.
Tying him to this
would be a chance
to put him away for good.
Not to mention a big win.
Looks like we have a new
long-range op on our hands.
Everybody go home.
get some sleep.
and tomorrow we will start
sitting on some stash houses.
You coming?
Uh. yeah.
I'll be right there.
Mr. Vega would like a word.
Thought you'd learned
your lesson. Counselor.
- Yeah?
What lesson is that. Hector?
Too ambitious.
You running and running
before you can walk.
Well. maybe that's
both of our problems.
Man. I seen your ass pull up
outside before you even parked.
I see it all. know it all.
Trust.
OK.
What do you think you know?
I know you hit a house
this afternoon.
Scooped up my boy.
Got D locked up.
- Oh. yeah. Diego.
He's real chatty.
That boy don't know nothing.
He only knows
what I let him know.
- My turn.
You know what I know?
You operate an interstate
drug trafficking network
selling fentanyl we can link
to 20 deaths so far.
The drugs are distributed
from stash houses
that you run here
all over New York.
where we seized 20 kilos
of your stash just today.
That's knowledge and intent.
agreement.
overt acts to constitute
a federal drug conspiracy.
This case is a slam dunk.
Your boss know you're here
working this so-called
slam dunk case?
See. it's funny...
you got a fantasy.
You're trying to get back at me
for how I did you wrong before.
Problem is.
if we did have other houses
like the one
you're talking about.
they already cleared out.
You ain't gonna find
nothing else on me.
The New York field office
is running
a large-scale
drug bust right now.
And the mug shot
that's pinned all the way
to the top of the org chart
is yours.
You really want
to try this again?
Do you want to come
at me a second time
and not catch me?
That's gonna be really bad
for you. isn't it?
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you put aside
this little beef
that you have with me. grow up.
and we work together?
Are you serious?
I could serve one
right up to you.
Dude's a menace.
Moving major weight.
- Yeah. what is he?
A competitor?
You want us to clear
the board for you?
Not even.
He's bringing in nitazene.
selling it in my city.
- You're drowning.
- No lie.
Synthetic opioids.
1.000 times more potent
than morphine.
You go to your boss.
you tell him
what we talked about.
My offer is simple...
we clean up the city together.
everybody wins.
and you. you climb out
of that little hole
that you dug for yourself.
Don't leave town.
Why would I?
We got work to do. Counselor.
It's been fun!
Come on. morning ambush
with no coffee?
What is it?
And that's it.
Vega has intel.
and he wants to trade it.
A nitazene network in New York.
If he's right. there'll be
more bodies than we can count.
Yeah. but I don't buy it.
I think he's just trying
to wriggle off the hook.
That's not your call.
Off-books surveillance.
no back-up.
Didn't just put
your job in jeopardy.
the case in jeopardy...
you took on a bunch
of unnecessary risk.
His name flashed up
on the board. Eva.
The three of us were doing
background on the guy.
You knew every single detail.
and you said nothing?
What is that?
You don't know what it's like.
- No?
So try me.
Hector Vega has been living
in my head rent-free for years.
I was a young prosecutor.
And I was too cocky to know
what I didn't even know.
And Vega was using his job at
a Paterson distribution center
to distribute product
across Jersey.
And he was smart.
It was pills and oxy.
And most of the evidence
was circumstantial.
And I had one witness.
a forklift driver. Joe Caruso.
And he was so scared.
You convinced him to testify?
I promised him.
with his testimony.
I could get Vega
once and for all.
And he had him killed.
A day before the trial.
Joe disappeared.
His body was never found.
I never proved it.
and Vega walked.
And you know what
the worst thing is?
I had to look Joe's wife
and his 9-year-old son
in the eye and tell them
the bad guy got away with it.
You can't carry that.
Look. I get it.
I know we have to take this
to Isobel.
But you have to have my back.
UNODC has issued
a Warning Advisory
about nitazene.
It has spread across Europe
like wildfire.
If it is. in fact.
here in New York
and Hector Vega can help us
stop the source.
we are going to listen.
Due respect.
Vega is a cockroach. OK?
This could just be
another angle that
he's trying to play.
- Right.
I think we trust. but we verify.
Do we have a problem here?
No.
Vega is smart enough to know
what happens if he cries wolf.
Regardless. I think we got
to run this thing down. no?
Agreed.
If he is right.
he gets the deal.
If he's wrong. he does his time.
So does this mean I'm out?
No.
No. I think
that you can be useful.
With Maggie on bereavement.
we are down an agent.
But you two need
to get on the same page.
You guys need to get
your house in order.
Agent Ramos.
we are going to work
with Vega to stop something
even bigger than him.
Do you understand?
- Yes. ma'am.
I expect you to put
the greater good
ahead of any personal crusade
or vendetta
you have against Vega.
That's our job.
For every one of us.
OK. this is a standard
Cooperation Agreement.
A lighter sentence in exchange
for your cooperation.
Now. seeing how
you poisoned two children.
I'd say this is
more than generous.
Your turf. your rules.
Ain't that right. Counselor?
Oh. my bad. I meant.
uh. Agent Ramos.
Let's get this straight.
Everything that you say.
we have to document
and prove in court.
All right?
So who's the source of this
nitazene that you claim
is being sold in New York?
- Jalen Turner.
But you ain't gonna
find him in your files
'cause he don't exist.
No priors. no picture.
Probably not even his real name.
But he is real.
and he's moving
some serious weight.
How serious?
Well. he's been slinging
8 balls since he was 12.
Moved up to keys
before he could drive.
And now
he's bringing in nitazene
that he designed himself.
Taught himself
a little chemistry.
And he's selling to kids
in my backyard
who're dumb enough
to try anything.
I want this guy gone.
- OK. how do we find him?
Dude's paranoid.
Never sleeps in the same bed
more than three nights.
And he's worked hard
to keep his name out
of your guys' mouths.
He's even killed for it.
- No one's untouchable. so...
- True.
Which is. uh.
why I know he's got
a shipment coming up off
a truck today from Culiacán.
You're really plugged in.
How do you know that?
Got a little spy inside
of Turner's network.
But I ain't gonna
let you near him.
You expose him. he dies.
We hear you.
Turner's a bad dude. man.
If you don't stop him.
you're gonna be
stacking bodies.
You understand?
OK.
That is an awful lot of
negative space on our workup.
- Agree.
"Jalen Turner" is very careful.
No idea if that's
his real name or a street name.
No arrests that match
the description Vega provided.
There is a Jalen Turner who
bounced around foster care
in New York and Connecticut.
If that's him.
he'd be about 50 now.
Anything from our friends
at the DEA?
Yes. they were able to confirm
the intel about the truck.
Vega's spy sent us
a photo of the 18-wheeler.
Here.
It crossed the border
at the Laredo Port
of Entry 36 hours ago.
Truck belongs to a vegetable
distributor. Calyer Wholesale.
All right. if we're gonna
substantiate our claims
about Jalen Turner's network.
we've got to find that truck
and track it back
to one of his strongholds.
I hate to say "but."
but we don't know
where it's going.
DEA has no known locations
for any stash house
operated by a Jalen Turner.
What about its distribution?
Where is it sold?
Anything that can put us onto
Turner's base of operation?
Working our sources.
but nitazene is still new
to New York.
FBI. NYPD. DEA...
zero leads on where
that truck is headed.
We do have one lead.
I told you guys
everything I know...
the truck. the route.
Listen. that truck stops
two times for gas. all right?
North Carolina and Jersey.
same gas station every time.
After that. when the truck
hits the city.
I don't know. man. Mars?
Yankee Stadium?
I got no clue.
Eyes on any of the stash houses?
I told you guys
that this guy was careful.
I mean. you guys are the FBI...
Patriot Act and whatnot.
I mean. you guys got cameras
everywhere and. what?
You really ain't
finding nothing?
Are you serious?
If we don't know where
the drugs are going.
we need to grab the shipment
before it gets to the city.
Dude. I'm telling you.
if the FBI stops that truck.
Turner goes underground.
He's gone.
You'll never find him.
The Feds cannot
touch that truck.
OK. fine.
The FBI won't touch that truck.
But the thing is.
truckloads like that
get robbed every day.
That'll be $11.43.
Can we get 30 bucks on Pump 3?
OK. any movement out there?
- Nothing yet.
Road's clear.
We don't know what
we're walking into.
Knowing Vega. there could be
another shoe to drop.
Elise just got a plate hit
six miles south.
This truck is coming. all right?
Turner could just
reroute the shipment.
Easy. partner.
It's no fun
when you're out of sync.
It's on me.
It's Vega.
he... he spins me out.
Look. Scola lost a partner.
He's trying to protect himself.
and he's trying to protect you.
And you kept him
at an arm's length.
Some friendly advice?
I. uh. wouldn't do that again.
not to him.
There's our shipment. guys.
Grab you a soda. or you want one
of those nasty energy drinks?
- Get out.
- Go! Down on the ground.
Walk forward.
On your knees.
Put your hands behind your head.
You do what you're told.
and you'll get
out of this alive.
- I got him. go.
Behind your back.
Stay inside and stay low!
Got it.
- You know who you're robbing?
- Shut up!
You got a vehicle
running in hot.
Oh. you're in trouble now.
Cover!
- Eva!
The truck!
Come on. Eva.
Eva!
I'm gonna have to jump.
Closer!
OK.
Got it?
- That's it.
Ah!
So what did you find?
Hector Vega's intel was good.
So there's drugs
inside the angels?
Well. technically.
the angels are the drugs.
in a manner of speaking.
You could touch them.
They're harmless in this form.
So the process is
called neutralizado.
chemical concealment.
Smugglers will use formulas
to break these drugs down
into their precursor components.
and then they'll shape them
into everyday items...
toilets. tools. toys.
Seems good for shipment.
but not for distribution.
Right.
Well. chemists will
reverse the process
at secondary extraction labs.
reconstitute the drugs.
You see that?
Positive for
aminoethyl chloride.
a nitazene precursor.
So the rip on Turner's
shipment was a success?
Not exactly.
All we have are
the precursor chemicals.
The angels on their own
aren't illegal.
That's true.
So to bust Turner.
we have to combine
this with the other ingredients
that he's shipping
into the city.
We have to track him down.
So these three phones
were recovered off
of Turner's guys
at the truck stop.
All three are burners.
and all of them
only called one number.
so we're assuming that's Turner.
So we are going
to dial the number.
If he picks it up.
this thing's on you.
It's gonna be a short call. man.
Well. then you better make
a good first impression.
You set a meet.
or the deal's off.
Hey. thanks to me.
you got the drugs. all right?
Thanks to you.
we almost got killed.
A precursor doesn't satisfy
your side of the agreement.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah.
All right. man. whatever.
I'll get you what you need.
Dial this bitch. all right?
Pest control.
- It's Hector Vega.
- Who?
Yeah. you know who I am.
Well. I found
your shipment. man.
Guys took it off you
down near exit 13.
and I thought
you might want it back.
Exit 13?
Yeah. these clowns didn't
know what they stepped in.
But. um.
I took it off their hands.
said I could get it
where it's supposed to be.
You missing some angels?
I don't know about any angels.
Package is worth 10 mil.
10 mil easy.
I'll tell you what.
You cut me in for 10%.
it's all yours.
Little finder's fee.
You do all of your business
on the phone. Mr. Vega?
The triangle off
of Union Avenue. 4:00 p.m.
What do you think. Ramos?
- I don't know.
- He'll be there.
He wants his stuff back.
OK. the meet
is five minutes out.
Everyone's in position.
We got eyes on the entire area.
SWAT is in position
and ready to move.
Unknown number.
- Must be Turner.
Put it on speaker.
I changed my mind.
- Wait. wait.
Hold up. man.
What you talking about?
He's about to switch up
locations.
Yes. he is.
I'm sending you a new spot.
You have 20 minutes.
He's sending us out to Queens.
He smells a trap.
He wants home field advantage.
OK. pulling up eye-in-the-sky
to get a layout of the area.
It's an abandoned mall.
Last tenant moved out
four years ago.
Scheduled to be demolished
later this year.
Are you sure you want to pivot
like this this late in the op?
We bail on him now.
Turner will get paranoid
and disappear.
- Eva. I get it. all right?
You want a win here.
You do not have to do this.
No. I think I do.
Isobel. what're we doing?
We have an opportunity.
We maintain focus
and take down our target.
Copy that.
Body cameras live.
Hey. when we get in there.
I'm in charge.
You got it?
No. you're not in charge.
You're just the mouth.
All right?
We're gonna handle the rest.
You can be mad all you want.
but let's not forget that
it's your offer
I took today. all right?
You better just back up off me
or go ahead
and violate my deal right now.
Eva. Vega is not our target.
- Hands up.
I need to search you.
Remember. we need confirmation
that he is in possession of
the second nitazene
precursor chemical
before we move in.
What can Turner see?
SWAT has to hang way back.
They'll be seen
if they cross Main.
Well. does the mall have any
cameras that we can piggyback?
Uh. connecting now.
Wait. hang on.
Yeah. it looks like Turner
has his own system in place.
I should be able to...
yeah. I'm in.
Hey. Ian. can you loop 'em?
- Yeah. I should be able to.
Stand by.
Might provide us cover
if things go sideways
and we need to move in.
Is that him?
I don't know.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Follow me.
Yo!
You Jalen Turner?
Hey. I'm talking to you.
homeboy.
You the dude or just some guy
he sent or what?
I'm here to recover
what was stolen.
We don't need to turn this
into a social visit.
This will be the one
and only time that we transact.
If I see you again after today.
you will not enjoy it.
Who the hell are you?
- Hey. hey. hey.
Don't talk to her like that.
That's my girl. all right?
Where's my money?
No product. no deal.
All right.
Show him.
This look familiar?
We got bags of these things
stashed somewhere
you'll never find.
You give us the cash. and
we'll give you the location.
You're forgetting
a crucial step.
I need to test the product.
Moment of truth.
We'll know if it's real
in approximately 60 seconds.
If it's red. you're dead.
Once we have confirmation
that he has made the nitazene.
SWAT can move in.
Not before then.
While we wait. one detail...
Regina. could you come out here?
Recognize any of these people?
You don't think I have people
all up and down the coast?
Take a good look.
Ring any bells?
Yeah. her.
She was there. all right.
- Eva's cover's been blown.
Get them out of there now!
You stole from me. and then
you sell back what was taken?
That's a short-timer mentality.
And short-timers
don't live long.
You want the deal or not?
Well. look at that.
At least you brought
back my supply.
Now where's the rest of it?
Somewhere safe.
You give us the cash.
and I'll give you the angels.
I have a counteroffer.
Your girl takes one of my guys.
gets the rest of my supply.
- This guy's funny.
Yeah?
And what am I
supposed to do. huh?
Just wait?
- No. I wait.
You don't.
All teams execute!
- Federal agents!
Stand down!
- FBI!
Stay where you are!
Turner's making a run for it.
We're pinned in.
- Same here.
Eva. you're the closest.
Eva. do you copy?
Stay on Turner.
- Don't move.
- Go.
Jalen Turner.
you're under arrest.
- Eva!
You all right?
You good?
Yeah.
Hey. where's Vega?
I left him at the meet.
OA. do you have eyes on Vega?
No.
His vest is here. but he split.
I'm sorry. Eva.
He got away.
Do you want the good news
or the bad news?
- There's good news?
- Sure.
Jalen Turner is off the street.
Shut down a major supplier
of a dangerous new drug.
But Hector Vega is in the wind.
DEA checked
every associated address...
ex-girlfriend. sister. mom.
If he's smart.
which we both know he is...
Yeah.
He's out of this city
and still moving.
His Pompeii fentanyl
killed two toddlers.
We'll get him. Eva.
He's the guy. huh?
Flipped the switch.
Made you want to go from
U.S. Attorney's Office
to the FBI?
When I heard his name yesterday.
I was right back there
to that same girl
who thought that
she was so clever.
Eva. you're not that girl.
You know why?
She didn't have me...
backing her up.
Have a good night.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm